# DIMITRIS RAMMOS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Hello, I am 21 years old and I live in Athens. I am an Junior Software Developer at Netcompany-Intrasoft. I am a Full Stack Developer and we coding with Java. I am a undergraduate student in Department of Informatics and Telecommunications, University of Athens. I am at 4th year of studies.

# CONTACT



+30 6940870953



jrammos@outlook.com.gr



www.linkedin.com/in/dimitrisrammos/



<u>DimitrisRammos</u>



My portfolio

# **EDUCATIONS**

# Department of Informatics and Telecommunications, NKUA

COMPUTER SCIENCE, OCT 2019 - PRESENT



# **SKILLS**

- Rust
- C/C++
- Java
- MySQL
- Python
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Git
- Assembly

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Check-In Agent**

GOLDAIR HANDLING, JUL 2021 - SEP 2021 - HERAKLION, GREECE

I was Check-In Agent for Aegean Airlines

#### **Associate Software Engineer**

WAPPIER, AUG 2022 - FEB 2023 - ATHENS, GREECE

I am a Backend developer and I code in Rust.

# **Junior Software Developer**

NETCOMPANY-INTRASOFT,
FEB 2023 - PRESENT - ATHENS, GREECE

I am a Full Stack developer and I am working on hospital medical file project(Java, Spring, PrimeFaces).

#### **PROJECTS**

- Tic Tac Toe\_- Game
- Role Playing Game Terminal Game
- Graph Coloring Project Project
- Artificial-Intelligence Project
- Compilers Project
- My Portfolio My WebPage

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### **HOBBIES**

- Greek Mother Tongue
- English Lower

Gym Box